两星期后 我离开越南
Two weeks later, I left Vietnam.
典礼已经开始
The ceremony was kicked off
首先是总统的演说
with a can did speech by the president
关于扩大越南战争的必要性
regarding the need for further escalation of the war in Vietnam.
约翰逊总统给四名军人颁发了荣誉勋章
Johnson awarded 4 Medals of Honor to men from each of the armed services.
美国深深地感谢你 孩子
America owes you a debt of gratitude, son.
我知道你受过伤
I understand you were wounded.
你的伤口在哪儿？
Where were you hit?
在屁股上 先生
In the but-tocks, sir.
嗯 那一定很好看
Well, that must be a sight.
我倒想瞧一瞧
I'd kinda like to see that.
“我献歌给你 罗宾森太太”
# And here's to you, Mrs. Robinson #
“耶稣对你也特别垂青”
#Jesus loves you more than you will know #
“上帝保佑你 罗宾森太太”
# God bless you, please, Mrs. Robinson #
老天 这孩子！
God damn, son!